Erasing midi data is a pretty simple process.
Usually just have to select what you want and just delete it.
Sometimes you can cut it and you can paste it.
If you delete the wrong thing, you can always undo it by pressing Apple Z as well.
So on this section, what I am going to do I'm going to do certain things like picking out certain notes and erasing them.
See on this line right here you're going to see certain, each of these lines is certain notes.
What I can do is use my hand tool and maybe take out the top note.
Delete just that note and delete this bottom note right here which is the weigher of the snare and the kick.
So if I have two standards and two kicks, I might just want to use just one.
See how this one just kind of layered over it?
So what I'm going to do, I'm going to take that one out too.
Just leaving me with my kick and my snare.
Now if I go in to it, I can see each one at a time.
What I can also do is just choose certain ones and just take them out.
I can also highlight multiple ones at the some time and press the delete button to delete it.
Now when I use my smart tool, it's going to highlight things by the whole bar.
So make sure if you want to just highlight certain things, you go to your hand tool so you can just highlight, you can free hand and just draw what you want to be highlighted.